[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p2",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p2",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 31,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Sun_p2",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 0,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 34,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 34,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 34,
  "Task": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p8",
  "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
  "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_title",
  "Description": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
 }
]